That's the third time you've
been reprimanded in court.
I bent a spoon with my mind.
What's the big deal?
You were testifying
a criminal case.
- You can't be playing tricks.
- It's all theater, right?
Bread and circuses?
Questions, Eve. Right here.
[indistinct shouting]
Eve!
- Eve, a couple of questions.
- 'I'll handle this, Eve.'
Ooh. That's Eve Mulberry.
The wine lady?
- 'She grows a great cabernet.'
- What's she accused of?
Killing her dance teacher.
They were lovers, I think.
Scandalous.
[cell phone ringing]
I gotta take this. Think about
what you wanna eat. Lisbon.
Deepest sympathies
for Mr. Ruiz's family.
'She's expressed that
on many occasions.'
[male #1]
'Eve, how you
feeling this morning?'
'Are you nervous at all
about closing arguments?'
Wouldn't you be?
Eve's facing
a lifetime in prison
'for a crime
she didn't commit.'
Eve, why don't you admit
that you killed Carlos Ruiz?
[male #2]
'Nice try, instead of
going for cheap reaction shots'
'you should be
following my case.'
[indistinct shouting]
CBI. Coming through. CBI.
Eve deserves praise
for her courage.
CBI. Eve! CBI. Quick question.
Do you love your mom and dad?
They passed away years ago.
But you think fondly of them.
Of course.
Thank you, everyone.
- 'Counsel, one more.'
- 'Eve.'
[male #3]
'Eve!'
Come on.
[Ardiles]
The defense has tried
to paint Eve Mulberry
as sweet as
the grapes she grows
'but you know
the facts of this case.'
[Ardiles]
'You know that
Eve was an adulterer'
even though she may
deny it...and you know
that her lover, Carlos,
blackmailed her for cash
and when Carlos Ruiz went back
to Eve to ask for more money..
...she beat his head into pulp.
Eve silenced her lover to
protect her marketable image.
But this..
...this is the work
of the real Eve.
[Ardiles]
'Take a good, long look..'
'then find her guilty.'
Ardiles. You got a second?
For you, Jane? I got two.
I'll come straight
out with it. You made a mistake.
Eve Mulberry.
- She isn't the killer.
- What are you playing at?
I'm not playing.
I'm just observing.
Eve's nonverbals
are screaming innocence
and sadness for the victim.
Thank you
for the observation.
- She loved her mom and dad too.
- There's more?
Women who murder were abused
by their parents. Not Eve.
When I mentioned them,
she looked to the left
she was tapped
into the brain's left side
where visual
memories are stored.
What if she
looked to the right?
Well, she would've been
accessing her creative mind
to fabricate a story.
This is it?
This is all your evidence?
Well, of course
there's my gut, too
but I didn't think
you'd take thatvery seriously.
That's the first correct
statement you've made.
I bet you a million dollars
she's innocent.
If I only had
the money.
[chuckles]
How about a nickel?
Jane, you understand this whole
conversation's pointless, right?
I mean, the jury's started
deliberating. It's over.
Well, the verdict
hasn't been read yet
so technically,
it's still on.
You know, unlike you
Eve Mulberry will not
get away with murder
so do us both a favor.
Don't mess with my case.
Oh, I won't mess with it.
I'm gonna fix it.
[theme music]
- There you are. We have to go.
- Where?
We have to talk
to Eve Mulberry. She's innocent.
Well, the jury may
feel differently.
Exactly. That's why we need
to find the real killer.
No. No way.
We don't have time to argue.
- This is not our problem.
- Justice isn't our problem?
The jury has heard arguments
for three months.
They're fully equipped
to determine the truth.
What if they don't?
An innocent woman gets punished
because you were eating.
- Hey, that's my sandwich.
- Mm-hmm?
Give it.
[instrumental music]
Can we help you?
We're with the CBI.
We'd like to talk to you.
No. No. No more police.
These might be my wife's
last hours of freedom.
We plan to spend
them alone. Thank you.
Oh, what if I could offer
a lifetime of freedom?
I know Eve's innocent.
I'd just like
the chance to prove it.
I'm sorry, whydo you
want to help me?
Well, let's just say
to whom much is given
much is expected. Yeah.
If you don't mind,
time is a factor here.
Is there somewhere
we can sit down and talk?
[Peter]
'I appreciate your
interest in my wife's case'
but what can you possibly do
at this stage of the game?
[Peter]
There's been
hundreds of hours of testimony.
[Jane]
Well, I'll let the courthouse
vultures pick over that carcass.
If I'm gonna help you,
I'm gonna need fresh meat.
Why did you take
dance lessons?
Peter's a wonderful dancer.
It was supposed
to be a surprise.
We're both so busy
all the time.
I thought it'd
bring us closer together.
And is that
how you met Carlos Ruiz?
At the dance lessons?
Yeah, that's right.
Ballroom, or, uh, salsa?
Tango.
Ah.
From what I've read
in the newspapers
you spent time with Carlos
outside of just the lessons.
There were
phone calls, meals..
Carlos and I were friends.
A Stanford-educated
winemaker
and a...dance instructor.
Just curious, um,
what'd you talk about?
I don't know. This and that.
You've lied to protect your
husband's feelings, haven't you?
Look at me, Eve.
I know you're feeling
guilt and shame.
I know what this might do
to your marriage
but, uh, the way I see it,
we're your last hope.
You have to trust us.
Honey, w-what is
he talking about?
- Why are you doing this?
- To help you.
You said you believed
I was innocent.
Of murder,
but you weren't hanging out
with your sexy dance teacher
for the stimulating chitchat.
You were attracted to him.
You danced the tango
with the man, for God sakes.
I did not have an affair.
That was a non-contracted
denial.
Truth tellers use contractions.
"I didn't have an affair."
This isn't the woman
I saw on the courthouse steps.
I think that you should leave.
It's like a band-aid, Eve.
Best to just
tear it off quickly.
It was just a few times.
Are you kidding me?
I'm s..
I'm so sorry.
Peter, you're so busy.
You're always traveling.
- I know that's not an excuse.
- You stay away from me now.
What's going on?
Eve just admitted
to sleeping with Carlos.
Oh.
I'm sorry I missed that.
And sorry,
who are these people?
CBI. They're here to help.
This is my best friend,
my business partner, Amy
and that's
my little sister Gretchen.
What about the blackmail?
You were sleeping with Carlos.
- Did you pay him off?
- 'No.'
He asked for a loan,
but I didn't give it.
- What was the money for?
- A business opportunity.
[Eve]
'I didn't really want to know.'
What are you
still doing here?
I mean,
besides brooding.
Pardon me?
Your wife dropped a bomb on you
and you're still standing.
If it were me, I'd be
out of here by now..
...unless, of course,
I suspected the, uh..
...affair all along.
Why would I hide
my suspicions?
Make yourself look good.
He's right.
If you had knowledge
of the affair
it would make you
a prime suspect.
- I didn't kill anyone.
- You used a contraction.
That's a hopeful sign, but I'll
keep an eye on you and you, Amy.
- Me?
- Eve confides in you.
She told you about the affair,
the best friend thing
unlike Gretchen.
She had no idea.
You do have issues with
your sister, though, don't you?
Duh. Like there are sisters
who don'thave issues.
I thought you said
these people were helping.
We are, and I'd say we're off
to a pretty solid start.
I think we need
some time alone.
[Lisbon]
We'll keep in touch.
[Rigsby]
'According to
the court transcript'
there was a cash deposit
for $20,000 paid
into Carlos Ruiz's bank account
the week of his death.
If we're taking Eve's word,
she didn't give him that.
He could've been involved
with something illegal.
Peter thought she was
having an affair?
Jane thinks so. It puts him
on the suspect list.
Peter Mulberry runs
a boutique investment firm.
Told the police
he was dinning
at his employee's homes
the murder night.
- The employee vouched for him.
- Dig deeper.
Who was the employee?
Do we trust him?
- Her.
- Exactly.
Don't know how we'll
get around the murder weapon.
[Kimball]
'That's a cutter mattock.'
Used for digging trenches
and cutting roots.
It's from Eve's vineyard. Her
fingerprints were all over it.
All this tells me is that
Eve might've been framed.
Make a list of anybody
who held a grudge against her.
Also look back
into Ruiz's phone records.
The original work from the
detectives looks a bit thin.
I know that this isn't
an official case, so thank you.
We're heading
to the crime scene.
Let me know
if you find anything out
and work fast, guys.
The jury's out.
[female #1]
'I ain't going anywhere.'
You know what?
Shut up! Get back in the house!
[female #1]
'Don't you walk away!'
[indistinct shouting]
Murder was months ago.
What kinda evidence
do you expect to find?
I'll know it when I see it.
Okay.
[intense music]
[knock on door]
[Lisbon]
'CBI. Open up.'
'Hello, police,
open up.'
What do you want?
Uh, w-were you
just watching me?
No, I wasn't.
[knock on door]
Step away from
the door, blondie.
Yeah, easy,
I-I-I'm-I'm with the CBI.
Do you think
I could come in?
"Consultant?"
What makes you think
I'd want a consultant here?
Well, how about a real cop?
I got one across the street.
[knock on door]
She'll be knocking all day.
Go get her.
I'll put on the kettle.
[whistles]
Lisbon!
[indistinct chattering]
- Back still hurting, huh?
- I got hit by a car, so yeah.
You should lay off
those pills.
You ever tried yoga?
My neighbor teaches it.
I can get you her number.
[sighs]
No, thanks.
Okay.
Let me know, yeah?
[gunshot]
Detective Silva?
That's right.
I'm Agent Van Pelt.
This is Agent Rigsby.
We're with the CBI.
Hey. How you doing?
Nice to meet you.
We've been looking
at your files on Eve Mulberry.
Oh, yeah?
That was some work, that case.
- Jury come back yet?
- No.
They're still
deliberating.
Eh, no worries.
That loon will get hers.
I love to watch the rich ones
fall, you know what I mean?
We were hoping you could help us
run down some information.
Yeah, sure.
What do you need?
Did you interview
a Conner Reilly?
Records state that Reilly spoke
with Carlos on the murder day.
Reilly...I don't remember.
What does my report say?
There's no notes on him.
Reilly.
Yeah. I remember.
We checked him out.
He looked clean.
Reilly had an alibi
for the murder night?
I guess. I don't recall.
You never talked
to him, did you?
What you getting on me for?
We called Reilly.
He didn't call back.
We were on Eve Mulberry by then.
Reilly didn't have a record.
No, no record,
no employment history
Facebook page,
not much of anything, really.
We tried calling Reilly but
his phone's been disconnected.
- It's like he never existed.
- What is your issue here?
This case
has already been tried.
We think Eve Mulberry
might be innocent.
Yeah? And why is that?
We have our reasons.
[chuckles]
It's that nut-job psychic
you guys work with, right?
Janet or Jane.
- He's showboating again, right?
- I feel sorry for you guys.
You're like, uh,
stooges in a comedy act.
- Yeah, he's not a psychic.
- Yeah, whatever.
Do you have
anything on Reilly?
Anything at all
that might help us find him?
Oh, let me think.
No. Sorry.
- Hey!
- Hey! I'm sorry.
[Lisbon]
'So you're home here
a lot, Mrs. Williams?'
[Williams]
'I am retired,
so, yes, I am.'
[Lisbon]
And, um..
were you home the night
that your neighbor was murdered?
I can see you've
lived here a long time
and you like to
keep an eye on things.
- Tell us what you saw.
- What are you doing over there?
- Admiring your lovely home.
- Oh.
Do you have help keeping,
uh, things so tidy?
No, I do not.
Do I look like an invalid?
Gloria. Why don't you
tell us what you saw?
I'll tell you what
I told the other police
stomping through my house.
I saw nothing.
- Okay, Lisbon. Let's go.
- I'm not done.
She's won't talk.
Look at her. She's scared.
That's why she hides
behind the curtains all day.
I'm not hiding from anyone.
I keep vigil over my house.
Well, there's no shame
in being afraid.
Old age can be
a terrifying time of life.
You're right. We should go.
Yes, thank you very much for
your time, ma'am. Thank you.
I saw someone.
-Oh.
- Ooh.
I saw, uh, a woman
the night that Mexican..
The Latino boy was murdered.
She went into the house, and
then minutes later, she ran out.
Can you describe her?
She had a tote bag.
She was slim build.
She had blonde hair,
long blonde hair.
She look like this?
Eve mulberry?
Yes, that's her.
Exactly. So there.
We can't quit now. I don't care
what the neighbor said.
An eyewitness identified
Eve as the killer.
Did you see a single
working clock there?
A wristwatch,
an alarm, anything?
No. So?
She lives cooped up here
with no sense of the time.
She probably confused the night
of the murder with another one.
So you're saying
she's flat-out wrong?
I'm just saying
Eve is innocent.
I need evidence to
keep the team on this.
We got a lead.
The victim talked
to a Conner Reilly
but Reilly was using
a phony social security number.
- It's an alias.
- Who for?
This guy. Terry Murphy.
He came over on a tourist visa
two years ago from Ireland.
[Rigsby]
'He's a tech scammer, internet
fraud, identity creation.'
He's violent.
He's been a murder suspect.
Ask, and you shall receive.
One of our CIs
has contacts there.
She's asking around now.
- Okay. We keep working.
- We should talk to Eve again.
Maybe she knows what was
going on with Murphy.
- Maybe.
- You're the boss on this one.
- Okay, don't be like that.
- Like what?
It's what you want.
What I want
is a little smile.
Well, you can't
have everything.
I checked out
the employee that was dining
with the husband
on the murder night.
And after the wife's
murder trial started
Peter Mulberry gave
the woman a huge promotion.
Suddenly she's
the company's youngest V.P.
- He bribed her for the alibi?
- Maybe. I'll keep digging.
Alright.
Summer. Welcome back.
I'm not gonna say
that I'm thebest
confidential informant ever
but I am pretty
high up on the list.
What do you have?
This girl
I used to hustle with..
...she's now into identify
theft. She knows Murphy.
I said that I had
some stolen information
to sell
and she made a call.
- Can she set up a meet?
- Already done.
Murphy will be at the Grafton
Street tavern in an hour.
Is it me,
or do you look impressed?
No, it's just you. We'll have
Summer wait at the bar.
When Murphy arrives,
we'll scoop him up.
If Summer gets Murphy to make an
offer that'd give us leverage.
I could do that.
It'll cost you extra.
All we have to do
is fit her with a wire.
Okay.
Just get him
to make the offer.
Excuse yourself to the bathroom.
That's it. Then we move in.
Okay.
Make the deal, hit the can.
Done and done.
That'll be $500,
$800 if I make the case.
I'll wire you up.
You again?
Uh, we're looking for Eve.
She just took
a walk with Amy
you might wanna
give her a minute.
Eve and Peter just had
an epic throw-down.
The waterworks
were ridiculous.
Okay. Well, you think
I can sample the goods?
Yeah, sure.
That is our new cab.
New to the business?
Is it that obvious?
You poured red wine
in a white wine glass.
Oh, well.
Yeah, I'm just helping out
here during the trial.
You don't own
a piece of the action?
Uh, no. The wine company belongs
to my sister and her BFF.
And who owns
the private villa?
Eve won that jackpot
when she married Peter.
All the land
belongs to him, so..
Gretchen,
that glass is wrong.
Your shoes are wrong
'but you don't see me
complaining about it.'
We've talked about this.
There's a reason investors
are knocking down the door.
It's an attention to detail.
Thank you. You haven't
taken any of the offers?
We go back
and forth about it.
From a business standpoint,
it makes sense.
But we don't want to be one of
those giant corporate vineyards
because then it wouldn't
be about the wine.
Yes, it's beautifully earthy,
with, uh..
...a hint of acid.
Do you notice
the tobacco note at the end?
- The cab's my favorite.
- Ah, yes. Mmm.
I'm sorry, could we speak
to Eve alone for a moment?
Gretchen, let's go.
Gladly.
Do you recognize this man?
No.
[Eve]
'Should I?'
His name's Terry Murphy.
He's a known criminal.
Carlos was in touch with him
the day of his murder.
Oh, my,
what kind of criminal?
[Lisbon]
'He's into
identity theft mostly'
but he's also done some illegal
surveillance and wiretapping.
What did Carlos have
to do with him?
Well, we were hoping
you'd tell us.
I wish I could, but this is good
news, right? This could help us.
I feel like the jury's gonna
walk outta that room any minute.
We're doing
everything we can.
Yeah. Very good. Thank you.
Do you realize,
every single time I deal
with your people,
things go to hell?
Osvaldo. Come in. Sit down.
Is there something in the water
here? I need to know.
I need to know
why your team is interfering
with a state murder trial.
I understand your anger.
No, you don't.
The state has spent
millions of dollars
not to mention
thousands of man-hours
prosecuting this case.
- And yet evidence was missed.
- What evidence?
The victim was in contact
with a violent criminal
the day of his murder.
That doesn't concern you?
No.
No, that's the concern
of an appeals court
if Mrs. Mulberry believes
that her due process was denied.
An appeals court. How long will
she have to spend in prison?
If she's innocent,
she deserves our help.
You want to know
why Jane took this case?
Because Eve loved her parents.
That's crazy, right?
I thought there was
something in the water
but I can see
the problem now.
It's you.
[rock music]
Testing, testing, one, two.
Kimball Cho's a wallaby.
[Kimball]
'Here's Murphy.'
[male #4]
'Beer?'
Summer, is it?
It is.
What do you got for me, girly?
A long list of numbers.
Social security, credit cards,
driver's license.
- About a hundred of each.
- Where do you get 'em?
Clients, the kinds
with high credit limits.
Won't know it hits them
till it's too late.
What sort of business you in?
[Summer]
'I'm a working girl.'
[Murphy chuckles]
Bang on.
You know, a little of your
honey would sweeten the pot.
$5,000 for the information.
Are you touched? Not here.
Wait. Let it play out.
Five thousand ain't gonna
happen, sunshine.
You'll get three.
That's the rate.
That's it. Let's move.
[Summer]
'How do I know I can trust you?'
[Murphy]
'You're questioning me?'
My name is my word.
Ask anyone I do business with.
Some friends of mine said that
you worked with Carlos Ruiz.
I'd ask him about you,
but...he's dead.
She's trying to make our case.
[Murphy]
'Well, now..'
You've got spirit,
I'll give you that.
[sighs]
You think so?
I was trying to act tough.
You never know
in these situations.
[both chuckle]
So what's the deal
with Carlos?
- Carlos?
- Yeah.
He had some plan to install
ATM skimmers in strip clubs.
Nice enough plan..
...got me to invest
20 grand in it..
Which he then spent
on strippers and booze.
So what'd you do?
What did Ido?
- Let's go.
- Just give her a minute.
[Summer]
'Yeah.'
'You didn't just let him
steal from you, did you?'
[gasps]
What's that to do
with you? Hmm?
Let go.
Where's that
list of numbers?
- Stop it.
- I want to see it now.
[door thuds]
Police! Don't move!
[both grunt]
[Kimball]
Hey!
[Rigsby]
'Give me your hands.
Hands behind your back.'
You alright?
You owe me $800.
Come on.
So a jury's deliberating
this case as we speak
and the $20,000
in Ruiz's bank account
is a key piece of evidence,
you gave it to him.
That's right. So what?
So I think you killed Carlos
because he lost your money.
That would be foolish.
If I killed him, I wouldn't
get it back, now, would I?
Don't mind me. Rigsby,
I brought you a cup of tea.
Uh, no, I'm good.
Thank you.
Oh. No good deed
goes unpunished. Uh, you?
Yous both seem
like agreeable men.
Can't we find a reasonable
solution to this problem?
Something that's
beneficial to all of us?
- He's trying to bribe us.
- Yeah, sounds like it to me.
Your words,
not mine...but..
...now you come to mention it..
...I do believe that everyone
has their price point.
What are you willing to pay?
If I'm out within the hour,
five grand to each of ya.
You killed a man.
You're not bribing your way out.
Certainly not
for 5 grand, anyhow.
I killed no man.
I deal in information,
not murder.
Yes, fake IDs, right?
Um..
How do the, uh,
fake identity things work?
- I always wanted to know.
- I'll explain it later.
Could you explain it now?
I mean, he's not gonna talk.
I understand it's a matter of
making a phony credit profile.
- 'That's all?'
- 'Yeah, that's all.'
If you were a hack,
that's all.
Well, what if you're not a hack?
How do you go about it then?
Huh? Theoretically speaking.
True identity farming is an art
that takes decades to set up.
You invent children.
Set up bank accounts
for them
file tax returns,
register them as voters
and then, years later,
you have the perfect identities
ready and waiting
for real people to step into.
That's it?
There's a cd
full of personal information
you have to fill out
first, but, uh..
Yeah, that's it.
And how much would one charge
for this, uh, particular..
'...thing? Theoretically.'
Well, now, we're talking
top of the line here.
Mm-hmm.
Two hundred thousand
for a brand-new you.
I'll get back to the
interrogation, if that's okay?
Yeah, by all means.
[Lisbon]
'Alright.
Thanks for the heads-up.'
Bad news. That was
a friend from the courthouse.
The jury didn't order dinner.
They're closing in on a verdict.
Hmm. We need to hustle.
Call Eve, have her come in
tell her you wanna update her.
- I'm springing Murphy.
- No. He's our prime suspect.
He didn't kill Carlos,
that doesn't mean
he can't be useful to us.
Uh...yeah.
Video surveillance equipment.
Those little cameras?
- I'm gonna need a few.
- Mind telling me one thing?
Like what I'm planning?
Yeah, that would be super.
[chuckles]
No?
You're annoyed
I didn't stick to the agenda
but all's well that
ends well. We're a team.
Stuff happens,
and, uh, we move on.
[sighs]
We're not a team.
Sign that.
Here's your final payment.
"Final payment?"
You were reckless and put
everyone in danger today.
If I can't trust you,
I can't use you.
So what, that's it?
You're done with me?
Yes.
Oh, you're back
for more, are you?
Do me a favor
and get us another cup of cha
with a bit of sugar
in it this time.
Get it yourself.
I pulled in a favor.
You're a free man..
...under one condition.
I need a new identity.
Do you, now?
Well, you wanted to know
my price point. That's it.
And I expect
a friends-and-family discount
from your usual fee.
How do I know
this isn't entrapment?
You don't, but try this.
You get me a new identity
or I'll book you
for receiving
stolen information.
That should be enough to get you
extradited back to Ireland
where you're wanted in
connection with two homicides..
...or is that three?
I'll do it for $100,000.
Okay, I'm in a tight spot.
How quickly can you work?
How quick can you
fill out the forms?
The cd, right.
When do I get that?
One hour.
There's a parking lot at
the south end of Fourth Street.
I'll meet you at the bottom
with the cd, but..
'...I'll need a deposit
to get me started.'
'Ten thousand.'
I'll send a courier.
As long as they've the cash.
Just don't be late.
[indistinct chattering]
- We're gonna have a contest.
- For what?
See who has
the best Irish accent.
Rigsby, you're up first.
Don't argue. We don't have time.
[clears throat]
I, um..
[Irish accent]
My name's Wayne Rigsby.
Why I'm talking with
an Irish accent right now, I..
...don't really know.
Uh, okay. Cho?
- No.
- Oh, come on.
We know you have
all sorts of hidden talents.
Rigsby it is, then.
Uh, practice learning this.
- Did you get those cameras?
- Yeah.
Good man. Thank you.
How are you two holding up?
Things have been better.
Lisbon, look at these.
What are those?
Wireless surveillance cameras.
The new owner of Carlos' house
was replastering the ceiling.
He found 'em
hidden everywhere.
Murphy was
a surveillance expert.
And Carlos owed
Murphy lots of money.
Well, maybe Murphy installed
the cameras to keep tabs on him.
Not "maybe."
We traced the serial numbers.
They were bought by one of
Murphy's established aliases.
If those were in the ceiling, it
could've recorded the murders.
Murphy might have
evidence on the real killer.
- It's possible.
- A bit of a long shot, right?
I'd say it's our only shot.
We just released Murphy.
I'm gonna bring him back in.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
You're gonna have to leave now.
- Of course. Thank you so much.
- Yeah, thank you.
- Well done.
- I try.
[Irish accent]
"Listen. Listen.
Do not interrupt."
Ready?
No, not really.
You go to war
with the army you have.
Read what's there,
and hang up.
Okay.
[Irish accent]
"Listen. Do not interrupt.
"I know who killed Carlos Ruiz,
and I've a video to prove it.
"for $10,000, I'll give you
this video on a cd.
"There's a parking lot at
the south end of Fourth Street.
- I'll be waiting for you in.."
- Forty five minutes.
Forty five minutes.
Don't be late.
- Bravo.
- The jury reached a verdict.
- When are they reading it?
- Six o'clock.
- Almost an hour. Shall we?
- Yeah.
It's been 45 minutes.
44.
Patience.
[tires screeching]
Hello.
[Lisbon]
'Okay, Murphy's here.'
Where are you?
[tires screeching]
[car door closes]
Hello.
Where's the money?
Ten thousand dollars.
It's all there.
Now the cd?
Where else
is the video stored?
Take it easy now.
Where else
is the video stored?
W-what video?
The video on the cd.
The video of the murder!
Where else is it stored?
What video? What murder?
You off your nut?
Amy. Put the gun down.
No, no. No, no.
Drop it!
- Now!
- You called me!
I-I know there's a video.
The cops told Eve there's a
murder video. I spoke to her.
I didn't call ya. There's no
video on there, you silly cow.
Okay, come on.
Let's make this snappy.
We got eight minutes to 6:00.
- You set all this up?
- Who set what up?
- What the hell's going on?
- Amy killed Carlos.
She thought your cd had
a video of the murder.
Bring Murphy
into the station
and book him for receiving
stolen information.
I'm taking Amy to court.
Seven minutes.
In the matter ofCalifornia
against Eve Mulberry
all rise for the honorable
Judge Isley Markman.
The jury's reached a verdict.
Bailiff, please bring them in.
- Hold on!
- 'What is going on there?'
Bailiff, remove those people.
Wait. We're with the CBI.
I know who you are.
He pulled
that mind reading trick
in my courtroom last month.
[Lisbon]
'I'm sorry to barge in'
but this is the woman
who killed Carlos Ruiz.
[Ardiles]
'They're showing contempt
for these proceedings.'
- This is an embarrassment.
- It's an embarrassment to you.
You had no idea
Amy framed Eve for murder.
Amy?
If you did this,
you have to say something now.
I want a lawyer first.
Enough.
Everyone in
my chambers now, except you.
My client is willing
to confess
but under one condition..
...the D.A.'s office takes
the death penalty off the table.
Well?
How did Jane know
that it was a frame job?
The neighbor saw a woman
with long blonde hair
leaving the victim's house
the night of the murder.
Jane knew that
Eve was innocent.
It had to have been
a woman in a wig.
Eve's sister, she couldn't
have pulled this off.
[Lisbon]
'She couldn't even
pour a glass of wine.'
'Amy was the only one
who was capable and had motive.'
Unbelievable.
Yeah. Death is off the table.
Start talking, young lady.
I just wanted
what was mine, you know?
Our wine is a sensation.
Everybody loves it.
Investors wanted
to jump on board
and they wanted
to make us rich.
And Eve wants to stay small.
Small? She has acres of land.
She has a rich husband.
What does she know about that?
I work nearly
a hundred hours a week.
I can barely make my mortgage.
[Amy]
'I thought this was my shot.'
And Eve had told you
about her affair with Carlos.
You knew, if he was killed,
she'd be investigated.
Yes.
I told Carlos
I was a friend of Eve's.
[Amy narrating]
I didn't know if someone
would see me so..
...I wore the wig
to make them think I was Eve.
I said I was interested
in taking dance lessons.
He invited me in.
And the murder weapon,
I took from our vineyard
I knew her fingerprints
would be on it.
[glass shattering]
What are you doing here?
I want my job back.
[dings]
Go home.
You know,
I was handling that situation
just fine today
until you busted in.
I need this job, Kimball.
I've given up everything else.
[elevator whirring]
Why would you
take this from me?
[paper rustles]
- Because you're crazy!
- What are you gonna do, huh?
- Hit me?
- No. That's what you want.
What?
That's why you kept
pushing Murphy today.
- What are you talking about?
- You get off on danger.
It provides a distraction
from your unhappy life!
Screw you, Kimball!
Y-you're not so difficult
to figure out yourself!
Yeah? What'd you
figure out?
Nothing! And it's
driving me crazy!
- Who are you?
- I gotta go.
No! No. No. No.
- Only if you give me my job.
- Move.
You fired me
because you like me.
You like me,
and don't know what to do.
- Admit it!
- Okay, I like you.
Admit it!
Oh.
I'm so sorry. Y-you do?
Can I go now?
[sighs]
Mmm.
[male #5]
'Were you astonished
by the verdict?'
[female #2]
'Eve, this way.'
[indistinct shouting]
[male #6]
'How about
a kiss for the cameras?'
[clapping]
Jane.
Your nickel.
Bet you're glad
you didn't bet a million.
Goodnight, Jane.
[shouting continues]
[theme music]